A terrified cat has survived a five -mile round -trip under the engine cover of a
car on a school run.
The black cat was found curled up under the engine cover of David King's car when he
decided to do an oil check after dropping his grandson off at school in Kent.
decided to do an oil check after dropping his grandson off at school in
The black cat was found curled up under the engine cover of David King's car when he
decided to do an oil check after dropping his grandson off at school in Kent.
Mr. King's wife said her husband had come running in and was shouting for me to come
have a look.
We weren't even sure it was alive, so I gently pushed it with a stick to check it
was breathing and saw it was a terrified little cat.
It reversed even further into the engine and was stuck.
I tried to reach it, but it was too far down and there wasn't any way I could get it
out. It reversed even further into the engine and was stuck.
tried to reach it, but it was too far down and there wasn't any way I could get it
I tried to reach it, but it was too far down and there wasn't any way I could get it
out. Following a rescue by UK charity Cats Protection,
the four -year -old cat was later reunited with its owner, Mr.
King's neighbor.